Markow Moussa

(615)-484-2172 | Middle Tennessee | Markow2010@yahoo.com LinkedIn - linkedin.com/in/markow-moussa-585b61250/ GitHub - github.com/markow2010

Professional Summary

Experiences with programming, building, designing, and testing computers, servers, and mining rigs. I am knowledgeable about Web 3.0 and the Metaverse. I possess experience in 5+ programming languages, while being exceptionally skilled in C++ and Python. Bilingual in English and Arabic.

Education

Tennessee Technological University, College of Engineering

Bachelor of Science, Computer Science

Technical Skills / Language's: C, C++, Python, HTML, MySQL, MATLAB, Linux

Cookeville, TN ted Graduation: 12/2023

Expected Graduation: 12/2023

Experience

nLync-Internship

Professional Tax Software company

- Went over multiple software plans with clients.
- Used 1040 Help Desk.

Murfreesboro, TN

- December 2022
- Reviewed code and future plans for the company.
- Studied Multiple Tax forms.

615.FireSales

Online/ Retail Seller

- Owner/Operator
- Marketing strategist.
- Data Analysist

McDonald's Manger

Shift Manager

- Trained and mentored new employees.
- Attentive to customer complaints.
- Reduced the waste amount by 20% each year to increase profit margin.

Wolverine Computer Repair

Volunteer Help (Full Time)

- Desktop and Laptop repairs.
- Information Acquisition.
- Troubleshooting.

Murfreesboro, TN

December 2021 - Current

- Increased sales by 42% monthly.
- Increased engagement on social media account to over 1500%.
- Inventory management

La Vergne, TN

October 2018 - December 2021

- Optimized kitchen process for greater efficiency.
- Maintained a high level of understanding of industry.
- Collaborated with other departments.

La Vergne, TN

August 2017 - May 2020

- Performed routine maintenance.
- Thorough attention to detail.
- Respected Privacy and documented the process.

Certifications

• CompTIA - IT Fundamentals

• Dell Certification - Client Course

Clubs

- Orthodox Christian Campus Ministries
- National Honor Society

- DECA Club
- Skills USA